{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Advanced Systems Integration and Architecture",
    "Term": "Finals",
    "Title": "Quality Management (QM)",
    "LastModified": "15 December 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "07 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This ensures the quality of the products, processes, and services right from the start",
      "answer": "SAP QM",
      "choices": [
        "SAP QM",
        "SAP CS",
        "SAP EAM",
        "SAP PS"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is designed to support companies in implementing and executing quality control processes by facilitating continuous process improvement, preventing product manufacturing errors, and implementing sustainable quality control programs",
      "answer": "SAP QM",
      "choices": [
        "SAP QM",
        "SAP CS",
        "SAP EAM",
        "SAP SAP"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM tool is used for creating and administering quality inspection plans?",
      "answer": "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Inspection (QM-IM)",
        "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
        "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tool involves using inspection specifications defined in quality planning to measure quality requirements?",
      "answer": "Quality Inspection (QM-IM)",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Inspection (QM-IM)",
        "Test Equipment Management (QM-IT)",
        "Archiving",
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM functionality is designed to prove that goods meet required quality measurements?",
      "answer": "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
        "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
        "Stability Study",
        "Archiving"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tool is used for capturing challenges and problems occurring during production or reported by customers?",
      "answer": "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
      "choices": [
        "Data Transfer",
        "Quality Control (QM-QC)",
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
        "Inspection using Multiple specifications"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM functionality allows the management of quality control processes?",
      "answer": "Quality Control (QM-QC)",
      "choices": [
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)",
        "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
        "Stability Study",
        "Quality Control (QM-QC)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM module manages information about test equipment used in inspections and ensures constant calibration?",
      "answer": "Test Equipment Management (QM-IT)",
      "choices": [
        "Archiving",
        "Test Equipment Management (QM-IT)",
        "Inspection using Multiple specifications",
        "Data Transfer"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which feature lets users inspect a batch of material against multiple inspection specifications?",
      "answer": "Inspection using Multiple specifications",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection using Multiple specifications",
        "Stability Study",
        "Archiving",
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tool documents requests to examine and test a product over time to study storage condition effects?",
      "answer": "Stability Study",
      "choices": [
        "Stability Study",
        "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
        "Archiving",
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which feature manages integration of the QM application component in logistical processes?",
      "answer": "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)",
      "choices": [
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)",
        "Quality Control (QM-QC)",
        "Data Transfer",
        "Quality Inspection (QM-IM)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM functionality removes data records for inspection documents no longer needed in the system?",
      "answer": "Archiving",
      "choices": [
        "Stability Study",
        "Test Equipment Management (QM-IT)",
        "Archiving",
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM tool ensures the transfer of large volumes of QM data efficiently to the SAP system?",
      "answer": "Data Transfer",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
        "Data Transfer",
        "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
        "Archiving"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM tool specifies the goods to be inspected, the inspection process, the characteristics to check, the equipment to use, and the standards to follow?",
      "answer": "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Inspection (QM-IM)",
        "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
        "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM functionality considers the different specific criteria set for goods by customers, may they be neutral?",
      "answer": "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
        "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
        "Stability Study",
        "Archiving"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tool can be configured to record, process, and manage positive information about the products and complaints about quality?",
      "answer": "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
      "choices": [
        "Data Transfer",
        "Quality Control (QM-QC)",
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
        "Inspection using Multiple specifications"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM functionality uses the results of this test to update the quality situation, control charts to manage characteristic values, and validate vendors for the purchasing procedure?",
      "answer": "Quality Control (QM-QC)",
      "choices": [
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)",
        "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
        "Stability Study",
        "Quality Control (QM-QC)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM module allows data for each test equipment to be maintained and ensures constant calibration?",
      "answer": "Test Equipment Management (QM-IT)",
      "choices": [
        "Archiving",
        "Test Equipment Management (QM-IT)",
        "Inspection using Multiple specifications",
        "Data Transfer"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM module is useful when testing for different clients or country requirements with their specific requirements?",
      "answer": "Inspection using Multiple specifications",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection using Multiple specifications",
        "Stability Study",
        "Archiving",
        "Control in Logistics (QM-PT-RP)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tool is used to explore the effects of various storage conditions on the characteristics of a product or substance?",
      "answer": "Stability Study",
      "choices": [
        "Stability Study",
        "Quality Planning (QM-PT)",
        "Archiving",
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP QM tool is useful for handling large volumes of data as it ensures efficient data transfer and consistency in the SAP system?",
      "answer": "Data Transfer",
      "choices": [
        "Quality Notification (QM-QN)",
        "Data Transfer",
        "Quality Certificate (QM-CA)",
        "Archiving"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SAP QM ensures higher customer satisfaction due to improved product quality.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Continuous quality assurance is not possible with SAP QM.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SAP QM provides certificates of quality as part of the product documentation to confirm product quality.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SAP QM cannot monitor supplier and customer returns.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Quality certificates in SAP QM are automated and printed at the time of delivery to the customer.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SAP QM enables permanent process monitoring alongside constant, flexible, and adaptable quality assurance processes.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "SAP QM does not help reduce failures and delays through failure analysis, risk minimization, or stability studies.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Required corrective actions can be activated automatically using SAP QM quality notifications.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP module is integrated with SAP QM by maintaining quality agreements?",
      "answer": "SAP Materials Management (MM)",
      "choices": [
        "SAP Sales and Distribution (SD)",
        "SAP Production Planning and Execution (PP)",
        "SAP Materials Management (MM)",
        "SAP Controlling (CO)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP module is integrated with SAP QM by maintaining quality information related to customers?",
      "answer": "SAP Sales and Distribution (SD)",
      "choices": [
        "SAP Controlling (CO)",
        "SAP Materials Management (MM)",
        "SAP Sales and Distribution (SD)",
        "SAP Production Planning and Execution (PP)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP module is integrated with SAP QM by performing inspection planning?",
      "answer": "SAP Production Planning and Execution (PP)",
      "choices": [
        "SAP Materials Management (MM)",
        "SAP Controlling (CO)",
        "SAP Production Planning and Execution (PP)",
        "SAP Sales and Distribution (SD)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which SAP module is integrated with SAP QM by integrating it with controlling processes?",
      "answer": "SAP Controlling (CO)",
      "choices": [
        "SAP Controlling (CO)",
        "SAP Sales and Distribution (SD)",
        "SAP Production Planning and Execution (PP)",
        "SAP Materials Management (MM)"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the independent environment in the system called?",
      "answer": "Client",
      "choices": [
        "Company Code",
        "Client",
        "Plant",
        "Purchasing Organization"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which organizational unit maintains a legal set of books?",
      "answer": "Company Code",
      "choices": [
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location",
        "Company Code",
        "Purchasing Group"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the operating area of a branch within the company called?",
      "answer": "Plant",
      "choices": [
        "Company Code",
        "Purchasing Organization",
        "Plant",
        "Client"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which unit allows differentiation between the various stocks of material in a plant?",
      "answer": "Storage Location",
      "choices": [
        "Storage Location",
        "Purchasing Organization",
        "Purchasing Group",
        "Client"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does the buying activity for a plant take place?",
      "answer": "Purchasing Organization",
      "choices": [
        "Company Code",
        "Storage Location",
        "Purchasing Organization",
        "Purchasing Group"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is responsible for procuring services and materials, and negotiating with vendors?",
      "answer": "Purchasing Organization",
      "choices": [
        "Purchasing Organization",
        "Storage Location",
        "Plant",
        "Purchasing Group"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What represents the buyer or group of buyers responsible for specific purchasing activities?",
      "answer": "Purchasing Group",
      "choices": [
        "Purchasing Group",
        "Company Code",
        "Plant",
        "Client"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What contains information for processing orders, deliveries, invoices, and customer payments?",
      "answer": "Customer Master",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Vendor Master",
        "Customer Master",
        "General Data"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Customer Master divided into?",
      "answer": "General Data, Company Code Data, and Sales Area Data",
      "choices": [
        "General Data, Company Code Data, and Sales Area Data",
        "General Data, Material Data, and Sales Area Data",
        "General Data, Material Data, and Employee Data",
        "General Data, Vendor Data, and Employee Data"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which master data contains information needed to manage a material?",
      "answer": "Material Master",
      "choices": [
        "Customer Master",
        "Material Master",
        "Vendor Master",
        "Sales Area Data"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which master data is used by most components within the SAP system, including Sales and Distribution?",
      "answer": "Material Master",
      "choices": [
        "Customer Master",
        "Material Master",
        "Vendor Master",
        "Purchasing and Accounting Data"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which master data contains information needed to do business with external suppliers?",
      "answer": "Vendor Master",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Vendor Master",
        "Customer Master",
        "Sales Area Data"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which departments primarily use and maintain Vendor Master?",
      "answer": "Purchasing and Accounting Departments",
      "choices": [
        "Sales and Distribution",
        "Materials Management",
        "Purchasing and Accounting Departments",
        "Quality Management"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What must a vendor have, just like a customer master?",
      "answer": "Master Record",
      "choices": [
        "Vendor Master",
        "Master Record",
        "Company Code Data",
        "General Data"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM process determines how a material can be processed further?",
      "answer": "Quality Information Record",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection Plan",
        "Quality Information Record",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Perform Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM process must be created if a quality assurance agreement or vendor release is required for a material?",
      "answer": "Quality Information Record",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection Plan",
        "Quality Information Record",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Perform Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM process checks whether a quality information record is required and available for the combination of material and vendor when a quotation or purchase order is created?",
      "answer": "Quality Information Record",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection Plan",
        "Quality Information Record",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Usage Decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which QM process defines which characteristics are to be inspected in each inspection operation and which test equipment is to be used?",
      "answer": "Inspection Plan",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection Plan",
        "Quality Information Record",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Usage Decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Several inspection plans with various inspection operations or inspection characteristics can be created for a material or combination of materials, vendors, manufacturers, or materials and customers",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records, processes, and manages information for a quality inspection?",
      "answer": "Inspection Lot",
      "choices": [
        "Material Management",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Usage Decision",
        "Perform Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a request to a plant to inspect a specific quantity of material or one or more pieces of equipment?",
      "answer": "Inspection Lot",
      "choices": [
        "Perform Inspection",
        "Usage Decision",
        "Quality Management",
        "Inspection Lot"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Under certain conditions, which component can automatically create inspection lots when materials are moved?",
      "answer": "QM component",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection Lot",
        "SAP system",
        "Sales and Distribution (SD)",
        "QM component"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "When can an inspection lot be automatically created for an inspection-relevant material?",
      "answer": "Delivery in SD component",
      "choices": [
        "Delivery in MM component",
        "Usage Decision",
        "Perform Inspection",
        "Delivery in SD component"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "To which different stocks can inspection lot stock be posted?",
      "answer": "Unrestricted Use, Scrap, Sample Usage, Block Stock",
      "choices": [
        "Block Stock",
        "Unrestricted Use, Scrap, Sample Usage, Block Stock",
        "Sample Usage",
        "Inspection Lot"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How is the inspection achieved in the inspection lot?",
      "answer": "By inspecting sample units",
      "choices": [
        "By checking the stock levels",
        "By performing quality analysis",
        "By inspecting sample units",
        "Inspection Lot"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What confirms that all physical samples have been evaluated and the inspection has been completed?",
      "answer": "Usage Decision",
      "choices": [
        "Perform Inspection",
        "Material Master",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Usage Decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What specifies whether the goods in the inspection lot have been accepted or rejected for use?",
      "answer": "Usage Decision",
      "choices": [
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Perform Inspection",
        "Inspection Lot Stock",
        "Usage Decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is achieved by inspecting sample units of the inspection lot and inspects the number of non-confirming sample units entered into the SAP system?",
      "answer": "Perform Inspection",
      "choices": [
        "Perform Inspection",
        "Material Master",
        "Inspection Lot",
        "Usage Decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is processed to create, update, and send requests for goods and services from vendors after the inspection plan?",
      "answer": "Purchase Order",
      "choices": [
        "Invoice",
        "Purchase Order",
        "Sales Order",
        "Outbound Delivery"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "After the purchase order is validated and meets the required characteristics, what happens next?",
      "answer": "Materials are received",
      "choices": [
        "Sales Order",
        "Goods Issue",
        "Usage Decision",
        "Materials are received"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What continues to the normal processes in SAP QM after materials are received?",
      "answer": "QM in Procurement",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Goods Receipt",
        "Perform Inspection",
        "QM in Procurement"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the Sales and Distribution (SD) process, what includes the physical removal or departure of products from a warehouse?",
      "answer": "Goods Issue",
      "choices": [
        "Invoice",
        "Outbound Delivery",
        "Purchase Order",
        "Goods Issue"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the physical acceptance of goods or materials into stock?",
      "answer": "Goods Receipt",
      "choices": [
        "Outbound Delivery",
        "Goods Issue",
        "Sales Order",
        "Goods Receipt"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "When is a goods receipt done?",
      "answer": "After the usage decision",
      "choices": [
        "After receiving materials",
        "After the Sales Order",
        "After Goods Issue",
        "After the usage decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What confirms that the materials have been evaluated and inspected?",
      "answer": "Usage Decision",
      "choices": [
        "Goods Receipt",
        "Sales Order",
        "Goods Issue",
        "Usage Decision"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is created once the materials result in positive quality management?",
      "answer": "Sales Order",
      "choices": [
        "Purchase Order",
        "Goods Issue",
        "Invoice",
        "Sales Order"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a contractual agreement between a sales organization and a sold-to-party in delivering products or services?",
      "answer": "Sales Order",
      "choices": [
        "Goods Receipt",
        "Outbound Delivery",
        "Purchase Order",
        "Sales Order"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is processed to contain all data required for triggering and monitoring the complete outbound delivery process?",
      "answer": "Outbound Delivery",
      "choices": [
        "Goods Receipt",
        "Sales Order",
        "Invoice",
        "Outbound Delivery"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is created to document the sales and confirm the request for payment from the vendor for delivered goods?",
      "answer": "Invoice",
      "choices": [
        "Outbound Delivery",
        "Sales Order",
        "Goods Issue",
        "Invoice"
      ],
      "reference": "07 Handout 1",
      "term": "Finals"
    }
  ]
}
